http://www.alliancefisheries.com/privacy-policy

Donate
Privacy PolicyAlliance of Communities for Sustainable FisheriesThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for alliancefisheries.org This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, i.e., reply back to your inquiry.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new things happening with us and/or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website (not recommended), your information is protected both online and offline.Should we ever collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information will be encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the our web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.CookiesWe use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies will allow your browser to easily re-establish our page when you are looking for us on the web. They also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site (Google Analytics). Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Also, you can set your browser to not accept cookies.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 831.373.5238 or via email, Kfosmark@aol.comPOSTED: January 2019
